A Guide to the Social Science Research Council records, Japanese Studies and Korean Studies, Record Group 3, Series 7 FA1775
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) grant and fellowship declinations and withdrawals, 1983-1996; 6; 1.8 Cubic Feet 4.5 document boxes: 1 legal size box and 3.5 letter size boxes
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Austin, Willard T., 1985-1986 (Box 68, Folder 1054)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1986-1987 declinations - Kim, Roy U., 1985-1986 (Box 68, Folder 1055)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1987-1988 declinations - Kim, Song-Chul, 1986-1987 (Box 68, Folder 1056)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1987-1988 declinations - Kim, Suk-Joon, 1986-1987 (Box 68, Folder 1057)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1987-1988 declinations - Choi, Insub, 1986-1987 (Box 68, Folder 1058)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1987-1988 declinations - Park, Chong-Min, 1986-1987 (Box 68, Folder 1059)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1987-1988 declinations - Park, Hea-young, 1986-1987 (Box 68, Folder 1060)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1987-1988 declinations - Korzeniewicz, Miguel, 1986-1987 (Box 68, Folder 1061)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1987-1988 declinations - Lee, Soo-Seong, 1986-1987 (Box 68, Folder 1062)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1987-1988 declinations - Paik, Won K., 1986-1987 (Box 68, Folder 1063)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1987-1988 declinations - Geisse, Guillermo, 1986-1987 (Box 68, Folder 1064)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1987-1988 declinations - Lee, Ok-jie, 1986-1987 (Box 68, Folder 1065)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1987-1988 declinations - Kim, Joong-Ryul, 1986-1987 (Box 69, Folder 1066)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1987-1988 declinations - Holman, James Martin, 1986-1987 (Box 69, Folder 1067)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 declinations - Lee, Chung-Myun and Kontuly, Thomas, 1986-1987 (Box 69, Folder 1068)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 declinations - Lee, Bong So, 1986-1987 (Box 69, Folder 1069)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 declinations - Lee, Byong Won, 1986-1987 (Box 69, Folder 1070)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 declinations - McNamara, Dennis L., 1986-1987 (Box 69, Folder 1071)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 declinations - Rosengren, William R., 1986-1987 (Box 69, Folder 1072)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 declinations - Slesnick, Daniel T., 1986-1987 (Box 69, Folder 1073)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 declinations - Won, George, 1986-1987 (Box 69, Folder 1074)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 declinations - Choi, Soonja, 1986-1987 (Box 69, Folder 1075)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 declinations - Choi, Sung-il, 1986-1987 (Box 69, Folder 1076)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 declinations - Clary, Brenda J., 1986-1987 (Box 69, Folder 1077)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 declinations - Kwon, Yoon-Hee, 1986-1987 (Box 69, Folder 1078)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1987-1988 declinations - Kalton, Michael C., 1986-1987 (Box 69, Folder 1079)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1989-1990 declinations - Back, Jong G., 1988-1989 (Box 69, Folder 1080)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1989-1990 declinations - Chin, Soo-Young, 1988-1989 (Box 69, Folder 1081)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1989-1990 declinations - Choi, Soo, 1988-1989 (Box 69, Folder 1082)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1989-1990 declinations - Chung, Jin-Young, 1988-1989 (Box 69, Folder 1083)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1989-1990 declinations - Chung, Moo Kwon, 1988-1989 (Box 69, Folder 1084)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1989-1990 declinations - Jun, Sang-In, 1988-1989 (Box 69, Folder 1085)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1989-1990 declinations - Kim, Jeongsook, 1988-1989 (Box 69, Folder 1086)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1989-1990 declinations - Kim, Manjae, 1988-1989 (Box 69, Folder 1087)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1989-1990 declinations - Kim, Seok-Joong, 1988-1989 (Box 69, Folder 1088)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1989-1990 declinations - Mulling, Craig, 1988-1989 (Box 69, Folder 1089)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1989-1990 declinations - Oh, Jisoo, 1988-1989 (Box 69, Folder 1090)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1989-1990 declinations - Park, Jae Young, 1988-1989 (Box 69, Folder 1091)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1989-1990 declinations - Park, Mee-Hae, 1988-1989 (Box 69, Folder 1092)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1989-1990 declinations - Shin, Wookhee, 1988-1989 (Box 69, Folder 1093)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1989-1990 declinations - Yang, Se-Jeong, 1988-1989 (Box 70, Folder 1094)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1989-1990 declinations - Yoo, Chul-In, 1988-1989 (Box 70, Folder 1095)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1989-1990 declinations - Hsaio, Frank, 1988-1989 (Box 70, Folder 1096)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1989-1990 declinations - Ogle, George, 1988-1989 (Box 70, Folder 1097)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1989-1990 declinations - Kim, John, 1988-1989 (Box 70, Folder 1098)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1989-1990 declinations - Kim, Seong Nae, 1988-1989 (Box 70, Folder 1099)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Research Planning Grant 1994-1995 declinations - Min, Eung-Jun (Box 71, Folder 1138)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Cheun, Wook-Jin (Box 70, Folder 1100)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Chung, Sangho (Box 70, Folder 1101)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Han, Jeong Woo (Box 70, Folder 1102)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Han, Jongwoo (Box 70, Folder 1103)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Han, Taehwan (Box 70, Folder 1104)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Jang, Soo Chan (Box 70, Folder 1105)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Kim, Hyosun (Box 70, Folder 1106)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Kim, Hyewon (Box 70, Folder 1107)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Kim, In-Young (Box 70, Folder 1108)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Kim, Shinhan (Sid) (Box 70, Folder 1109)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Koh, Helen (Box 70, Folder 1110)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Lee, Seongwoo (Box 70, Folder 1111)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Lee, Sungkyun (Box 70, Folder 1112)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Lee, Yoonmi (Box 70, Folder 1113)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Lui, Yuen-fan (Box 70, Folder 1114)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Oppenheim, Robert (Box 71, Folder 1115)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Park, Hankyoung (Box 71, Folder 1116)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Seo, Jinyoung (Box 71, Folder 1117)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Song, Kui-hee (Box 71, Folder 1118)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Yang, Hyunah (Box 71, Folder 1119)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Dissertation Fellowship 1995-1996 declinations - Yun, Hye-ran (Box 71, Folder 1120)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Blackman, Nancy (Box 71, Folder 1121)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Choe, In-Soo (Box 71, Folder 1122)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Choi, Yearn Hong (Box 71, Folder 1123)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Hoffman, Diane (Box 71, Folder 1124)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Hyun, Kyoung Ja (Box 71, Folder 1125)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Kim, Min-Sun (Box 71, Folder 1126)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Pak, Nomyon (Box 71, Folder 1127)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Whiting, Van Robert (Box 71, Folder 1128)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - London, Bruce (Box 71, Folder 1129)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - McGuire, James (Box 71, Folder 1130)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Min, Pyong Gap (Box 71, Folder 1131)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Advanced Research Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Kim, Seung-chul and Scherling, Steven (Box 71, Folder 1132)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Research Planning Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Suh, Dae-Sook and Lee, Chae-Jin (Box 71, Folder 1134)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Research Planning Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Anderson, Barbara (Box 71, Folder 1135)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Research Planning Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Miller, Elisa (Box 71, Folder 1136)
  - Joint Committee on Korean Studies (JCKS) Research Planning Grant 1995-1996 declinations - Min, Eung-Jun (Box 71, Folder 1137)